To save their future, he must fight his fate.
2:22 is a science fiction, mystery, thriller film directed by Paul Currie.
Two planes almost collide after a blinding flash of light paralyzes
air traffic controller Dylan Branson for a few seconds.
Suspended from his job, Dylan starts to notice an ominous pattern of sounds and events that
repeats itself in exactly the same manner every day, ending precisely at 2:22 p.m.
Also drawn into a complex relationship with a woman, Dylan must figure out a way
to break the power of the past and take control of time itself.
Dylan Branson, played by Michiel Huisman.
Sarah Barton, played by Teresa Palmer.
Jonas Edman, played by Sam Reid.
Bill, played by John Waters.
Catherine Mills, played by Kerry Armstrong.
Inky, played by Richard Davies.
2:22 is a 2017 science fiction thriller film directed by Paul Currie, written by Nathan
Parker and Todd Stein, and starring Michiel Huisman, Teresa Palmer and Sam Reid.
The film's plot involves air traffic controller Dylan Branson, who, thanks to a mysterious anomaly at 2:22,
prevented the collision of two aircraft and met Sarah, whose destinies appear to be tied to the time 2:22.
The film was released in theaters and on VOD on June 30, 2017.
The film explores themes of new york city, deja vu, airport, birthday, routine.
The tone is intense and emotional and thought_provoking.